
export default [
       {
           customer:[
            {
                question: 'What does pawndr does to ensure safety ?',
                answer: 'When it comes to safety, pawndr offers trained professionals (private contractors), with each pet, livestock or animal handling. Each driver has their own pet insurance and liability policy  in case of any accidents, loss or injuries.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Can i track my order?',
                answer: 'Customers are also provided with live gps tracking so they can see where their transports are at all times.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Where can  I get a receipt for my booking(s)?',
                answer: 'You can receive and review your receipt transactions through our app, through email or SMS.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What information does Pawndr Share?',
                answer: 'Pawndr is developed in accordance with best practices for building secure web applications. We employ the latest technology and hardware to ensure that your data is secure. We do not under any circumstances share any personal information to any other third parties without the consent of the customer or driver. Please review are policy on cookies and data usage for more information.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What is pawndr review policy?',
                answer: 'Open and honest communication is the foundation of every great relationship. , We love when our pet, animal and livestock owners leave reviews on Pawndr. Honest feedback helps us to improve our service for customer satisfaction.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Should I tip a Valet Driver?',
                answer: 'Booking through Pawndr will always be cashless and convenient. That said, if you’d like to offer them a tip, you’re perfectly welcome to! Just know that it’s never expected or required. However, we do find that tipping is also a great incentive and appreciation for hard work.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How does booking on pawndr works?',
                answer: 'Booking your pickup or delivery is very easy process. You indicate the pick up and delivery locations, time,  then payment . After payment, relax as your delivery or pickup is taken care by experienced drivers. It is essential that you communicate with your designated Valet driver to ensure all details are covered for your upcoming trip. Communication is key for a successful trip.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Pawndr is in how many states?',
                answer: 'Panwdr is available in all 48 states. Excluding Hawaii and Alaska. We expect to expand to both Hawaii, Alaska and Canada at a later time depending on their specific needs. ',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Can I do repeat booking?',
                answer: 'Yes! You can do repeat booking with our easy-to-use application. You can do a repeat booking in days, weeks, months or year. We offer an incentive program for repeat bookings to get a free booking after 7 bookings with us.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Can I monitor the process of my booking?',
                answer: 'Absolutely, you can monitor your booking process, as you can communicate with our drivers during the pickup and delivery timeframe.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What is your cancellation policy?',
                answer: 'At Pawndr, we understand mistakes and emergencies happen. Due to the nature of our service, for us and the drivers involved, time is money. We have a 48 hour cancellation policy for bookings placed 3 days or more in  advance. For days or times sooner or under 3 days we have a 12 hour cancellation policy. For bookings cancelled within or after these time frames, we charge a 25% cancellation fee based on your trip quote.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What Services does Pawndr Offer?',
                answer: 'We offer services like Pet pickup and delivery and Livestock pickup and delivery and exotic animal  pick up and delivery with restrictions on highly dangerous or endangered species.',
                open: false
              },
            ],

           driver:[
            {
                question: 'How can I become a Valet Driver?',
                answer: 'Interesting in driving with us or expanding your transport business? Look no further, with our easy sign up and application process you can start driving and earning in no time! You must first past both our driver certification and background check and qualification criteria.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Why should I become a Valet Driver?',
                answer: 'You can make your own schedule and be your own boss while making uncapped earnings as a driver. You will also learn skills essential for operation and for your career.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How long will it take for pawndr to review my profile?',
                answer: 'You profile is reviewed between 3-5 working days.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How do I verify my identity?',
                answer: 'After applying to be a driver, we conduct a thorough background check and require both photo I.D, social security and social media account references. Once approved you will be verified.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What are the service fees?',
                answer: 'For drivers , we take 18% of every order you accept and complete. We also offer a $9.99 monthly subscription.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What is pawndr?',
                answer: 'Panwdr is a tech platform that connects drivers to customers for pick ups and deliveries for pets and livestock. We offer other services for pets animals and livestock. Check our app for updates on services you may need.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What are Pawndr’s Terms of service?',
                answer: 'Kindly visit our Terms of Service Page for answers to this question.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Are drivers employees of Pawndr?',
                answer: 'No, drivers are not employees of pawndr. Drivers are private contractors (1099) and operate under their own identities. Drivers are solely responsible for all services rendered.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How can I contact Pawndr Support?',
                answer: 'You can contact Pawndr support at support@gopawndr.com for any questions, concerns or just to say hi! We don’t bite.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How can I view my profile? ',
                answer: 'On our dedicated app, you can edit and update your profile by a click on the edit profile on pawndr app, edit your profile and save.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How can I manage my Calendar?',
                answer: 'You can manage your calendar on your driver app. Navigate to the calendar menu on the sidebar, set days when you will be available to get booking and days you will be unavailable.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How can I manage my inbox?',
                answer: 'On pawndr’s dedicated app, you can manage your inbox, by navigating to the inbox section on the sidebar, read messages, also get booking notifications.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How do I issue an invoice or be available for repeat booking?',
                answer: 'You can issue invoice to a pet or livestock owner on our dedicated app, by sending it directly to their emails and also as SMS.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'How can I view my total earnings?',
                answer: 'Navigate, to the statistics menu of the sidebar, navigate to check earnings, earnings expected, etc.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What can I do if I have concerns about the wellbeing of a pet or livestock in my car?',
                answer: 'We recommend always, to contact your customer directly if you have any questions or concerns. Drivers can also contact support for any questions on how to handle situations and or concerns about a specific pet, animal or livestock. Please do not ignore a serious or unusual situation. Using common sense is an essential part of being both and excellent driver and solving problems.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'What if there is an emergency?',
                answer: 'If there is an emergency please call 911 or visit your nearest veterinary clinic for any animal related issues. We also recommend contacting both your customer and support to keep up date on the situation.',
                open: false
              },
              {
                question: 'Do I have to take pictures or video of pets during a trip?',
                answer: 'We highly recommend taking pictures, video and also keeping in constant communication with your customers. This not only ensures safety but builds trust between you and the customers',
                open: false
              },
           
            ]
        }
]
    
